export default
[
    {
        "id": "hotspot-1",
        "title": 1,
        "question": "נקודה זו היא:",
        "options": [],
        "answer": "esophagus",
        "dataSurface": "5 0 205 206 203 0.399 0.522 0.079",
        "userAnswer": ""
    },
    {
        "id": "hotspot-2",
        "title": 2,
        "question": "נקודה זו היא:",
        "options": [],
        "answer": "liver",
        "dataSurface": "1 0 62 64 65 0.046 0.639 0.314",
        "userAnswer": ""
    },
    {
        "id": "hotspot-3",
        "title": 3,
        "question": "נקודה זו היא:",
        "options": [],
        "answer": "stomach",
        "dataSurface": "5 0 11 10 9 0.682 0.249 0.069",
        "userAnswer": ""
    },
    {
        "id": "hotspot-4",
        "title": 4,
        "question": "נקודה זו היא:",
        "options": [],
        "answer": "gallbladder",
        "dataSurface": "7 0 134 131 132 0.690 0.174 0.135",
        "userAnswer": ""
    },
    {
        "id": "hotspot-5",
        "title": 5,
        "question": "נקודה זו היא:",
        "options": [],
        "answer": "ascending colon",
        "dataSurface": "0 0 1052 1117 1106 0.105 0.327 0.569",
        "userAnswer": ""
    },
    {
        "id": "hotspot-6",
        "title": 6,
        "question": "נקודה זו היא:",
        "options": [],
        "answer": "transverse colon",
        "dataSurface": "0 0 3855 3790 3789 0.528 0.223 0.249",
        "userAnswer": ""
    },
    {
        "id": "hotspot-7",
        "title": 7,
        "question": "נקודה זו היא:",
        "options": [],
        "answer": "descending colon",
        "dataSurface": "0 0 7114 7116 7101 0.284 0.215 0.502",
        "userAnswer": ""
    },
    {
        "id": "hotspot-8",
        "title": 8,
        "question": "נקודה זו היא:",
        "options": [],
        "answer": "sigmoid colon",
        "dataSurface": "0 0 9309 9245 9244 0.743 0.003 0.254",
        "userAnswer": ""
    },
    {
        "id": "hotspot-9",
        "title": 9,
        "question": "נקודה זו היא:",
        "options": [],
        "answer": "rectum",
        "dataSurface": "0 0 10395 10383 557 0.670 0.272 0.058",
        "userAnswer": ""
    },
    {
        "id": "hotspot-10",
        "title": 10,
        "question": "נקודה זו היא:",
        "options": [],
        "answer": "anus",
        "dataSurface": "0 0 10490 10508 10506 0.864 0.003 0.133",
        "userAnswer": ""
    },
    {
        "id": "hotspot-11",
        "title": 11,
        "question": "נקודה זו היא:",
        "options": [],
        "answer": "small intestine",
        "dataSurface": "4 0 2167 2168 2169 0.335 0.308 0.356",
        "userAnswer": ""
    },
    {
        "id": "hotspot-12",
        "title": 12,
        "question": "נקודה זו היא:",
        "options": [],
        "answer": "pharynx",
        "dataSurface": "2 0 270 271 272 0.625 0.304 0.072",
        "userAnswer": ""
    },
    {
        "id": "hotspot-13",
        "title": 13,
        "question": "נקודה זו היא:",
        "options": [],
        "answer": "larynx",
        "dataSurface": "2 0 231 228 229 0.610 0.253 0.137",
        "userAnswer": ""
    }
  ]